BOUNCE, ROCK, SKATE, ROLL
Roll Bounce is a comedy, drama, family film directed by Malcolm D. Lee.
In the summer of 1978, a teenager and his group of friends face new challenges when their
neighborhood roller-skating rink closes, forcing them to visit a different rink.
Xavier 'X', played by Shad Moss.
Junior, played by Brandon T. Jackson.
Curtis Smith, played by Chi McBride.
Boo, played by Marcus T. Paulk.
Naps, played by Rick Gonzalez.
Mixed Mike, played by Khleo Thomas.
Roll Bounce is a 2005 American comedy-drama film written by Norman Vance Jr.
and directed by Malcolm D.
The film stars hip hop artist Bow Wow as the leader of a
roller skating crew in 1970s Chicago.
The film also includes Nick Cannon, Meagan Good, Brandon T.
Jackson, Wesley Jonathan, Chi McBride, Kellita
Smith, Jurnee Smollett and Mike Epps.
The name of the film is derived from the 1979 song "Bounce,
Rock, Skate, Roll" by Vaughan Mason & Crew.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.